Guide to the Human Service Employees Registration and Voter Education Fund (Human SERVE) records,
Rare Book and Manuscript Library Columbia University Libraries
- Series X: National Organizations
  - Election Center, 1992-1999 (Box 9, Folder 425)
  - Election Data Services (Box 9, Folder 426)
  - Election Watch (Box 9, Folder 427)
  - Endorsing Agency-based Voter Registration (Box 9, Folder 428)
  - 1199 (Box 9, Folder 429)
  - Family Service America (FSA) (Box 9, Folder 430)
  - Fare SHARE (Box 9, Folder 431)
  - FRONTLASH (Box 9, Folder 432)
  - Funders' Committee for Voter Registration & Education (Box 9, Folder 433)
  - Girl Scouts of USA (Box 9, Folder 434)
  - Hadassah (Voter Challenge Guide) (Box 9, Folder 435)
  - Hispanic Elected Local Officials (HELD) (Box 9, Folder 436)
  - Independent Sector Voter Registration (Box 9, Folder 437)
  - Industrial Areas Foundation (Box 9, Folder 438)
  - Institute for Social Research (Box 9, Folder 439)
  - International Association of Clerks, Recorders, Election Officials, & Treasurers (Box 9, Folder 440)
  - International Center on Election Law & Administration (Box 9, Folder 441)
  - International Institute of Municipal Clerks (Box 9, Folder 442)
  - Initiative Resource Center (Box 9, Folder 443)
  - Institute for Southern Students (Box 9, Folder 444)
  - Joint Center for Political Studies, 1986-1987 (Box 9, Folder 445)
  - Joint Center for Political Studies, 1988-1995 (Box 9, Folder 446)
  - Labor Council for Latin American Advancement (Box 9, Folder 447)
  - LEAD or LEAVE (Box 9, Folder 448)
  - Leadership Conference on Civil Rights (Box 9, Folder 449)
  - League of Rural Voters (Box 9, Folder 450)
  - League of United Latin American Citizens (LULAC) (Box 9, Folder 451)
  - League of Women Voters, 1983-1994 (Box 9, Folder 452)
  - League of Women Voters, 1995-1997 (Box 9, Folder 453)
  - M.T.V. Networks (Box 10, Folder 454)
  - McDonald's (Box 10, Folder 455)
  - Mexican American Legal Defense and Education Fund (Box 10, Folder 456)
  - Moral Majority Report (Box 10, Folder 457)
  - Midwest Voter (Box 10, Folder 458)
  - Mobilization for Survival (Box 10, Folder 459)
  - National Abortion Federation (Box 10, Folder 460)
  - National Abortion Rights Action League (NARAL) (Box 10, Folder 461)
  - The National Assembly (Box 10, Folder 462)
  - NAACP Legal Defense Fund (Box 10, Folder 463)
  - National Association for the Advancement of Colored People (Box 10, Folder 464)
  - National Association of Attorneys General (Box 10, Folder 465)
  - National Association of Black County Officials (Box 10, Folder 466)
  - National Association of Child Care Resource & Referral Agencies (Box 10, Folder 467)
  - National Association of Community Health Centers, 1983-1987 (Box 10, Folder 468)
  - National Association of Community Health Centers, 1988-1996 (Box 10, Folder 469)
  - National Association of Counties (Box 10, Folder 470)
  - National Association of Housing & Redevelopment Officials (Box 10, Folder 471)
  - National Association of Korean Americans (Box 10, Folder 472)
  - National Association of Latino Appointed & Elected Officials (Box 10, Folder 473)
  - National Association of Secretaries of State's award to Human SERVE (Box 10, Folder 474)
  - National Association of Secretaries of State (NASS), 1983-1985 (Box 10, Folder 475)
  - National Association of Secretaries of State, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 476)
  - National Association of Secretaries of State, 1987 (Box 10, Folder 477)
  - National Association of Secretaries of State, 1988 (Box 10, Folder 478)
  - National Association of Secretaries of State, 1989-1990 (Box 10, Folder 479)
  - National Association of Secretaries of State, 1991 (Box 10, Folder 480)
  - National Association of Secretaries of State, 1992 (Box 10, Folder 481)
  - National Association of Secretaries of State, 1993-1994 (Box 10, Folder 482)
  - National Association of Secretaries of State Awards, 1995 (Box 10, Folder 483)
  - National Association of Secretaries of State, 1995-1996 (Box 10, Folder 484)
  - National Association of Secretaries of State, 1997-1998 (Box 10, Folder 485)
  - National Association of Social Workers, 1983-1986 (Box 10, Folder 486)
  - National Association of Social Workers, 1987-1994 (Box 10, Folder 487)
  - National Association of Social Workers, 1995-1997 (Box 10, Folder 488)
  - National Association of State Election Directors, 1989-1995 (Box 10, Folder 489)
  - National Association of State Election Directors, 1996-1998 (Box 10, Folder 490)
  - National Association of Women's Centers (Box 10, Folder 491)
  - National Black Caucus of State Legislators (Box 10, Folder 492)
  - National Black Leadership Roundtable (Box 10, Folder 493)
  - National Civic League (Box 10, Folder 494)
  - National Coalition for the Homeless (Box 10, Folder 495)
  - National Coalition on Black Voter Participation (Box 10, Folder 496)
  - National Community Education Association (Box 10, Folder 497)
  - National Committee for Responsive Philanthropy (Box 10, Folder 498)
  - National Committee for Full-Employment (Box 10, Folder 499)
  - National Committee for an Effective Congress (NCEC) (Box 10, Folder 500)
  - National Community Action Foundation (Box 10, Folder 501)
  - National Coalition of Abortion Providers (Box 10, Folder 502)
  - National Commission on Working Women (Box 10, Folder 503)
  - National Conference of Black Mayors (Box 10, Folder 504)
  - National Conference of Community Health Centers (Box 10, Folder 505)
  - National Conference of State Legislatures, 1983-1987 (Box 11, Folder 506)
  - National Conference of State Legislatures, 1988-1992 (Box 11, Folder 507)
  - National Conference of State Legislatures, 1993-1995 (Box 11, Folder 508)
  - National Conservative Political Action Committee (Box 11, Folder 509)
  - National Council of La Raza (Box 11, Folder 510)
  - National Council of Senior Citizens (Box 11, Folder 511)
  - National Education Association (Box 11, Folder 512)
  - National Emergency Mobilization on the Right to Vote (Box 11, Folder 513)
  - National Family Planning & Reproductive Health Association (Box 11, Folder 514)
  - National Forum for Black Public Administrators (Box 11, Folder 515)
  - National Governors Association, 1985 (Box 11, Folder 516)
  - National Governors Association, 1986-1988 (Box 11, Folder 517)
  - National Governors Association, 1989-1991 (Box 11, Folder 518)
  - National Hispanic Leadership Conference (Box 11, Folder 519)
  - National Hispanic Leadership Institute (Box 11, Folder 520)
  - National Issues Forums (Box 11, Folder 521)
  - National Lawyers Guild (Box 11, Folder 522)
  - National League of Cities, 1984-1986 (Box 11, Folder 523)
  - National League of Cities, January 1987-May 1987 (Box 11, Folder 524)
  - National League of Cities, June 1987-October 1987 (Box 11, Folder 525)
  - National League of Cities, November 1987- December 1987 (Box 11, Folder 526)
  - National League of Cities, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 527)
  - National League of Cities, 1989-1993 (Box 11, Folder 528)
  - National Lesbian & Gay Health Association (Box 11, Folder 529)
  - National League of United Latin American Citizens (Box 11, Folder 530)
  - National League for Nursing (Box 11, Folder 531)
  - National Low Income Housing Coalition (Box 11, Folder 532)
  - National Multiple Sclerosis Society (Box 11, Folder 533)
  - National Municipal League (Box 11, Folder 534)
  - National Organization for Women (Box 11, Folder 535)
  - National Organization on Disability (Box 11, Folder 536)
  - National People's Action (Box 11, Folder 537)
  - National Policy Institute (Box 11, Folder 538)
  - National Puerto Rican Coalition (Box 11, Folder 539)
  - National Student Campaign for Voter Registration (NSCVR) (Box 11, Folder 540)
  - National Student Education Fund (Box 11, Folder 541)
  - National Training and Information Center (Box 11, Folder 542)
  - National Union of Hospital & Health Care Employees (Box 11, Folder 543)
  - National Urban Coalition (Box 11, Folder 544)
  - National Voting Rights Museum & Institute (Box 11, Folder 545)
  - National Women's Health Network (Box 11, Folder 546)
  - National Women's Political Caucus (Box 11, Folder 547)
  - New England Association of City and Town Clerks (Box 11, Folder 548)
  - New York State Network for Voter Registration (Box 11, Folder 549)
  - Northeast Citizen Action Resource Center (Box 11, Folder 550)
  - Northwest Voter Registration (Box 11, Folder 551)
  - Operation Big Vote (Box 11, Folder 552)
  - Orthopsychiatric Association (Box 11, Folder 553)
  - Patriotic Majority (Box 11, Folder 554)
  - Peace Links (Box 11, Folder 555)
  - People for the American Way (Box 11, Folder 556)
  - Philipino American Heritage Federation (Box 11, Folder 557)
  - Physicians for Social Responsibility (Box 11, Folder 558)
  - Planned Parenthood, 1980-1983 (Box 11, Folder 559)
  - Planned Parenthood, 1984 (Box 11, Folder 560)
  - Planned Parenthood, 1985-1986 (Box 11, Folder 561)
  - Planned Parenthood, 1987-1989 (Box 11, Folder 562)
  - Planned Parenthood, 1990-1995 (Box 11, Folder 563)
  - Planned Parenthood, 1996-1997 (Box 11, Folder 564)
  - Poverty & Race Research Action Council (Box 12, Folder 565)
  - The President's Committee on Employment of People With Disabilities (Box 12, Folder 566)
  - Progressive Constituency Network (Box 12, Folder 567)
  - Project 500 (Box 12, Folder 568)
  - Project Vote, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 569)
  - Project Vote, 1983 (Box 12, Folder 570)
  - Project Vote, 1984 (Box 12, Folder 571)
  - Project Vote, 1985 (Box 12, Folder 572)
  - Project Vote, 1986 (Box 12, Folder 573)
  - Project Vote, 1987-1996 (Box 12, Folder 574)
  - Public Citizen (Box 12, Folder 575)
  - Public Media Center (Box 12, Folder 576)
  - Puerto Rican Legal Defense and Education Fund (Box 12, Folder 577)
  - Push Literacy Action Now (PLAN) (Box 12, Folder 578)
  - Rainbow Coalition (Box 12, Folder 579)
  - Rock The Vote, 1990-1991 (Box 12, Folder 580)
  - Rock The Vote, 1992-1996 (Box 12, Folder 581)
  - The Rural Coalition (Box 12, Folder 582)
  - Society for Public Health Education (Box 12, Folder 583)
  - Social Service Employees Union, The Unionist (Box 12, Folder 584)
  - Southern Organization Committee (Box 12, Folder 585)
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference (Box 12, Folder 586)
  - Smithsonian Institution Traveling Exhibition Service (Box 12, Folder 587)
  - Southern Regional Council, 1985-1992 (Box 12, Folder 588)
  - Southern Regional Council, 1993 (Box 12, Folder 589)
  - Southern Regional Council, 1994-1996 (Box 12, Folder 590)
  - Southwest Organizing Project (Box 12, Folder 591)
  - Southwest Voter Registration Education Project (Box 12, Folder 592)
  - State Issues Forum (Box 12, Folder 593)
  - Students Organizing Students (Box 12, Folder 594)
  - Student Voter Education Fund (Box 12, Folder 595)
  - Swing Vote, 1996 (Box 12, Folder 596)
  - Taft Institute (Box 12, Folder 597)
  - The Teamsters (Box 12, Folder 598)
  - Third Wave (Box 12, Folder 599)
  - Travelers Aid (Box 12, Folder 600)
  - 20/20 Vision (Box 12, Folder 601)
  - United Automobile Workers (CAP) (Box 12, Folder 602)
  - United Church of Christ (Box 12, Folder 603)
  - United Hospital Fund of New York (Box 12, Folder 604)
  - United Parents Associations (Box 12, Folder 605)
  - United Methodist Church (Box 12, Folder 606)
  - USA Votes (Box 12, Folder 607)
  - United States Conference of Mayors, 1983-May 1986 (Box 12, Folder 608)
  - United States Conference of Mayors, June 1986-December 1986 (Box 12, Folder 609)
  - United States Conference of Mayors, January 1987-June 1987 (Box 12, Folder 610)
  - United States Conference of Mayors, July 1987-December 1987 (Box 12, Folder 611)
  - United States Conference of Mayors, 1988-1993 (Box 12, Folder 612)
  - U.S. Public Interest Research Group (Box 12, Folder 613)
  - United States Student Association (Box 12, Folder 614)
  - United Way (Box 12, Folder 615)
  - United Way/United Auto Workers (Box 12, Folder 616)
  - Urban League (Box 12, Folder 617)
  - Vote America (Box 13, Folder 618)
  - Voters for Choice Education Fund (Box 13, Folder 619)
  - Voter Education Project (Box 13, Folder 620)
  - Voter Research and Surveys (Box 13, Folder 621)
  - Western States Center (Box 13, Folder 622)
  - The Women's Trust (Box 13, Folder 623)
  - Wider Opportunities for Women (Box 13, Folder 624)
  - Women's Action Alliance (Box 13, Folder 625)
  - Women's Action for Nuclear Disarmament (Box 13, Folder 626)
  - Women's Campaign Fund (Box 13, Folder 627)
  - Women's Equity Action League (Box 13, Folder 628)
  - Women Executives In State Government (Box 13, Folder 629)
  - Women USA (Box 13, Folder 630)
  - Women's Vote Project, November 1983-March 1984 (Box 13, Folder 631)
  - Women's Vote Project, April 1984-August 1988 (Box 13, Folder 632)
  - Women Work Conference (Box 13, Folder 633)
  - Youth Policy Institute (Box 13, Folder 634)
  - YWCA (Box 13, Folder 635)
- Series XI: Labor
  - AFL-CIO (Box 13, Folder 636)
  - American Federation of State, County, and Municipal Employees (AFSCME) (Box 13, Folder 637)
  - Communications Workers of America (CWA) (Box 13, Folder 638)
  - Early Involvement (Box 13, Folder 639)
  - Financial Support (Box 13, Folder 640)
  - Industrial Union Council/International Union of Electrical Workers (Box 13, Folder 641)
  - Information Kit (Box 13, Folder 642)
  - International Association of Machinists (Box 13, Folder 643)
  - National Association of Letter Carriers (Box 13, Folder 644)
  - New Jersey (Box 13, Folder 645)
  - New York (Box 13, Folder 646)
  - District Council 37, New York, 1983-1988 (Box 13, Folder 647)
  - District Council 37 Scandal, New York (Box 13, Folder 648)
  - Service Employees Internation Union (SEIU) (Box 13, Folder 649)
  - Teamsters (Box 13, Folder 650)
  - Transportation Communications International Union (Box 13, Folder 651)
  - United Auto Workers (Box 13, Folder 652)
  - United Food and Commercial Workers International Union (Box 13, Folder 653)
  - Implementation: All Unions, May 20, 1993-May 23, 1995 (Box 13, Folder 654)
  - Implementation: All Unions, June 1, 1995-August 30, 1997 (Box 13, Folder 655)
- Series XII: States
  - Alabama, 1984-1985 (Box 13, Folder 656)
  - Alabama, 1986-1987 (Box 13, Folder 657)
  - Alabama, 1988 (Box 13, Folder 658)
  - Alabama, 1990-1993 (Box 13, Folder 659)
  - Alabama, January 1994-August 1994 (Box 13, Folder 660)
  - Alabama, September 1994-December 1994 (Box 13, Folder 661)
  - Alabama, 1995-1997 (Box 13, Folder 662)
  - Alaska, 1984-1996 (Box 13, Folder 663)
  - Arizona, 1983-1987 (Box 13, Folder 664)
  - Arizona, January 1988-May 1988 (Box 14, Folder 665)
  - Arizona, June 1988-December 1988 (Box 14, Folder 666)
  - Arizona, 1989-1990 (Box 14, Folder 667)
  - Arizona, 1991 (Box 14, Folder 668)
  - Arizona, 1992-1993 (Box 14, Folder 669)
  - Arizona, 1994-1997 (Box 14, Folder 670)
  - Arkansas, 1984-1987 (Box 14, Folder 671)
  - Arkansas, 1988-1991 (Box 14, Folder 672)
  - Arkansas, 1992-1993 (Box 14, Folder 673)
  - Arkansas, 1994-1995 (Box 14, Folder 674)
  - California, 1982-1983 (Box 14, Folder 675)
  - California, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 676)
  - California, 1985 (Box 14, Folder 677)
  - California, 1986 (Box 14, Folder 678)
  - California, January 1987-April 1987 (Box 14, Folder 679)
  - California, May 1987-December 1987 (Box 14, Folder 680)
  - California, January 1988-August 1988 (Box 14, Folder 681)
  - California, September 1988-December 1988 (Box 14, Folder 682)
  - California, 1989 (Box 14, Folder 683)
  - California, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 684)
  - California, 1991-1992 (Box 14, Folder 685)
  - California, 1993 (Box 14, Folder 686)
  - California, January 1994-May 1994 (Box 14, Folder 687)
  - California, June 1994-December 1994 (Box 14, Folder 688)
  - California, January 1995-May 1995 (Box 14, Folder 689)
  - California, June 1995-November 1995 (Box 14, Folder 690)
  - California, 1996 (Box 15, Folder 691)
  - California: Fraud, 1998 (Box 15, Folder 692)
  - California, Alameda County, 1986-1988 (Box 15, Folder 693)
  - California, Irvine, 1987-1988 (Box 15, Folder 694)
  - California, Los Angeles, 1983-1987 (Box 15, Folder 695)
  - California, Los Angeles, 1988-1993 (Box 15, Folder 696)
  - California, Oakland, 1987-1988 (Box 15, Folder 697)
  - California, Santa Ana, 1988 (Box 15, Folder 698)
  - California, Santa Clara, 1987-1989 (Box 15, Folder 699)
  - California, San Diego, 1987-1989 (Box 15, Folder 700)
  - California, San Francisco, 1984-1994 (Box 15, Folder 701)
  - California, West Hollywood, 1987-1988 (Box 15, Folder 702)
  - California, [No Dates] (Box 15, Folder 703)
  - Colorado, 1983-1984 (Box 15, Folder 704)
  - Colorado, 1985-1987 (Box 15, Folder 705)
  - Colorado, 1988-1996 (Box 15, Folder 706)
  - Connecticut, 1983 (Box 15, Folder 707)
  - Connecticut, 1984 (Box 15, Folder 708)
  - Connecticut, 1985-1986 (Box 15, Folder 709)
  - Connecticut, 1987-1988 (Box 15, Folder 710)
  - Connecticut, 1989-1990 (Box 15, Folder 711)
  - Connecticut, 1991-1993 (Box 15, Folder 712)
  - Connecticut, 1994-1998 (Box 15, Folder 713)
  - Delaware, 1985-1995 (Box 15, Folder 714)
  - Delaware, 1996 (Box 15, Folder 715)
  - District of Columbia, 1983-1988 (Box 15, Folder 716)
  - District of Columbia, 1989 (Box 15, Folder 717)
  - District of Columbia, 1990-1996 (Box 15, Folder 718)
  - Florida, 1983-1985 (Box 15, Folder 719)
  - Florida, 1986 (Box 15, Folder 720)
  - Florida, 1987-1989 (Box 15, Folder 721)
  - Florida, 1990-1991 (Box 15, Folder 722)
  - Florida, 1992 (Box 15, Folder 723)
  - Florida, 1993 (Box 15, Folder 724)
  - Florida, 1994 (Box 15, Folder 725)
  - Florida, 1995-1996 (Box 15, Folder 726)
  - Georgia, 1984-1986 (Box 15, Folder 727)
  - Georgia, 1987 (Box 15, Folder 728)
  - Georgia, 1988 (Box 16, Folder 729)
  - Georgia, 1989-1990 (Box 16, Folder 730)
  - Georgia, 1991-1993 (Box 16, Folder 731)
  - Georgia, 1994 (Box 16, Folder 732)
  - Georgia, 1995 (Box 16, Folder 733)
  - Georgia, 1996-1997 (Box 16, Folder 734)
  - Hawaii, 1984-1994 (Box 16, Folder 735)
  - Idaho, 1984-1985 (Box 16, Folder 736)
  - Idaho, 1986-1995 (Box 16, Folder 737)
  - Illinois, 1993-February 1984 (Box 16, Folder 738)
  - Illinois, March 1984-November 1984 (Box 16, Folder 739)
  - Illinois, 1985-1986 (Box 16, Folder 740)
  - Illinois, 1987 (Box 16, Folder 741)
  - Illinois, 1988-1989 (Box 16, Folder 742)
  - Illinois, 1990 (Box 16, Folder 743)
  - Illinois, 1991-1992 (Box 16, Folder 744)
  - Illinois, 1993 (Box 16, Folder 745)
  - Illinois, January 1994-May 1994 (Box 16, Folder 746)
  - Illinois, June 1994-December 1994 (Box 16, Folder 747)
  - Illinois, January 1995-March 1995 (Box 16, Folder 748)
  - Illinois, April 1995-June 1995 (Box 16, Folder 749)
  - Illinois, July 1995-December 1995 (Box 16, Folder 750)
  - Illinois, 1996 (Box 16, Folder 751)
  - Illinois, Chicago, Cook County, 1991 (Box 16, Folder 752)
  - Indiana, 1984-1987 (Box 16, Folder 753)
  - Indiana, 1988-1989 (Box 16, Folder 754)
  - Indiana, 1990-1992 (Box 16, Folder 755)
  - Indiana, 1993 (Box 16, Folder 756)
  - Indiana, 1994-1995 (Box 16, Folder 757)
  - Iowa, 1984-1987 (Box 16, Folder 758)
  - Iowa, 1988-1989 (Box 17, Folder 759)
  - Iowa, 1990-1995 (Box 17, Folder 760)
  - Kansas, 1983-1993 (Box 17, Folder 761)
  - Kansas, 1994 (Box 17, Folder 762)
  - Kansas, 1995 (Box 17, Folder 763)
  - Kentucky, 1982-1988 (Box 17, Folder 764)
  - Kentucky, 1989-1992 (Box 17, Folder 765)
  - Kentucky, 1993-1998 (Box 17, Folder 766)
  - Louisiana, 1984-1987 (Box 17, Folder 767)
  - Louisiana, 1988-1993 (Box 17, Folder 768)
  - Louisiana, 1994 (Box 17, Folder 769)
  - Louisiana, 1995-1997 (Box 17, Folder 770)
  - Maine, 1984-1990 (Box 17, Folder 771)
  - Maine, 1991-1996 (Box 17, Folder 772)
  - Maryland, 1983-1986 (Box 17, Folder 773)
  - Maryland, 1987-1990 (Box 17, Folder 774)
  - Maryland, 1991-1995 (Box 17, Folder 775)
  - Maryland, 1996 (Box 17, Folder 776)
  - Massachusetts, 1983 (Box 17, Folder 777)
  - Massachusetts, January 1984-February 1984 (Box 17, Folder 778)
  - Massachusetts, March 1984-December 1984 (Box 17, Folder 779)
  - Massachusetts, January 1986-September 1986 (Box 17, Folder 780)
  - Massachusetts, October 1986-December 1986 (Box 17, Folder 781)
  - Massachusetts, 1987 (Box 17, Folder 782)
  - Massachusetts, 1988 (Box 17, Folder 783)
  - Massachusetts, 1989-1990 (Box 17, Folder 784)
  - Massachusetts, 1991-1994 (Box 17, Folder 785)
  - Massachusetts, 1995 (Box 18, Folder 786)
  - Massachusetts, 1995 (Box 18, Folder 787)
  - Massachusetts, January 1996-March 1996 (Box 18, Folder 788)
  - Massachusetts, April 1996-January 1998 (Box 18, Folder 789)
  - Michigan, 1972-1983 (Box 18, Folder 790)
  - Michigan, 1984 (Box 18, Folder 791)
  - Michigan, 1985-1986 (Box 18, Folder 792)
  - Michigan, 1987-1989 (Box 18, Folder 793)
  - Michigan, 1990-1993 (Box 18, Folder 794)
  - Michigan, January 1994-July 1994 (Box 18, Folder 795)
  - Michigan, August 1994-December 1994 (Box 18, Folder 796)
  - Michigan, 1995 (Box 18, Folder 797)
  - Michigan, 1996-1997 (Box 18, Folder 798)
  - Minnesota, 1984-1985 (Box 18, Folder 799)
  - Minnesota, 1986 (Box 18, Folder 800)
  - Minnesota, 1987 (Box 18, Folder 801)
  - Minnesota, 1988 (Box 18, Folder 802)
  - Minnesota, 1989-1995 (Box 18, Folder 803)
  - Mississippi, 1985-1987 (Box 18, Folder 804)
  - Mississippi, 1988 (Box 18, Folder 805)
  - Mississippi, 1989-1991 (Box 18, Folder 806)
  - Mississippi, 1992-1994 (Box 18, Folder 807)
  - Mississippi, 1995 (Box 18, Folder 808)
  - Mississippi, 1996 (Box 18, Folder 809)
  - Mississippi, 1997-1998 (Box 18, Folder 810)
  - Missouri, 1984-1996 (Box 18, Folder 811)
  - Montana, 1984-1991 (Box 18, Folder 812)
  - Montana, 1992-1997 (Box 18, Folder 813)
  - Nebraska, 1985-1989 (Box 18, Folder 814)
  - Nebraska, 1991-1996 (Box 18, Folder 815)
  - Nevada, 1983-1988 (Box 19, Folder 816)
  - Nevada, 1989-1993 (Box 19, Folder 817)
  - New Hampshire, 1982-1988 (Box 19, Folder 818)
  - New Hampshire, 1991-1993 (Box 19, Folder 819)
  - New Hampshire, 1994 (Box 19, Folder 820)
  - New Hampshire, January 1995-May 1995 (Box 19, Folder 821)
  - New Hampshire, June 1995-1996 (Box 19, Folder 822)
  - New Jersey, No Dates (Box 19, Folder 823)
  - New Jersey, April 1983-March 1984 (Box 19, Folder 824)
  - New Jersey, April 1984-December 1984 (Box 19, Folder 825)
  - New Jersey, January 1985-August 1985 (Box 19, Folder 826)
  - New Jersey, September 1985-December 1985 (Box 19, Folder 827)
  - New Jersey, 1986 (Box 19, Folder 828)
  - New Jersey, 1987 (Box 19, Folder 829)
  - New Jersey, 1988 (Box 19, Folder 830)
  - New Jersey, 1989 (Box 19, Folder 831)
  - New Jersey, 1990 (Box 19, Folder 832)
  - New Jersey, 1991 (Box 19, Folder 833)
  - New Jersey, 1992 (Box 19, Folder 834)
  - New Jersey, 1993 (Box 19, Folder 835)
  - New Jersey, January 1994-September 1994 (Box 19, Folder 836)
  - New Jersey, October 1994-December 1994 (Box 19, Folder 837)
  - New Jersey, 1995 (Box 19, Folder 838)
  - New Jersey, January 1996-May 1996 (Box 19, Folder 839)
  - New Jersey, June 1996-1998 (Box 19, Folder 840)
  - New Jersey, Bergen County, 1983-1986 (Box 19, Folder 841)
  - New Jersey: Election Day Registration, August 1985-September 1985 (Box 19, Folder 842)
  - New Jersey: Election Day Registration, October 1985-October 1988 (Box 20, Folder 856)
  - New Jersey: Disabilities (Box 20, Folder 857)
  - New Jersey: Election Day Workers (Box 20, Folder 858)
  - New Jersey: Fundraising, 1983-1985 (Box 20, Folder 859)
  - New Jersey:Fundraising, 1986-1987 (Box 20, Folder 860)
  - New Jersey: GOTV (Box 20, Folder 861)
  - New Jersey: Health/Hospital, 1983-1985 (Box 20, Folder 862)
  - New Jersey: Health/Hospital, 1986-1988 (Box 20, Folder 863)
  - New Jersey: Health/Hospital Counties (Box 20, Folder 864)
  - New Jersey: Legal, 1982-1984 (Box 20, Folder 865)
  - New Jersey: Legal, 1985-1990 (Box 20, Folder 866)
  - New Jersey: Legislation (Box 20, Folder 867)